filerack.in 2011-08-10

# Filerack.in - Easy One Click File Hosting

Privacy Policy 

Filerack.in respects the privacy of users and is committed to protect their privacy in all respects. For more information please contact us. The present privacy policy governs the online information collection practices of Filerack.in. This privacy policy, including our children's privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means. To register for full access to the Site and in certain areas of the Site (for example, on contest entry pages), where personal information is requested, you may be asked for your age or birth date. You hereby agree that all information you provide to us regarding age verification shall be truthful, accurate, and complete. This privacy policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user and/ or member information collected on the Site. Filerack.in provides this privacy policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or discontinue using the Site. This privacy policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Filerack Terms of Use. Your use of the Filerack.in Site and any personal information you provide on the Site remains subject to the terms of this privacy policy and our Terms of Use. Please note that any video, image, comment or other content posted on the Site becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information which is subject to this privacy notice. Please read this privacy policy carefully. By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of the Site, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this privacy policy and our Terms of Use 

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or including all that you submit to the Site you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 
  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

**Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

**How do we protect your information?**  

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Filerack.in and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Filerack.in makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If Filerack learn of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Filerack.in may post a notice on the Site if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us using this link Privacy Policy. 

**Do we use cookies?**  

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. When you visit the Filerack.in Site, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Site may not function properly.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, and keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.  
In addition, third party advertisers or third party ad servers that place and present advertising on the Site also may collect information from you via cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies. These third party advertisers and ad servers may use the information they collect to help present their advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness, or for other uses. The use and collection of your information by these third party advertisers and ad servers is governed by the relevant third party's privacy policy and is not covered by our privacy policy. Indeed, the privacy policy of these third party advertisers and ad servers may be different from our privacy policy.

Like, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**Terms Of Use**

Please also visit our Terms of use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [Click Here](http://www.filerack.in/index.php?page=tos). 

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  

We reserve the right at any time to: change the terms of this Agreement; change the Services, including eliminating or modifying any content on or feature of the Site; or change/charge any fees or charges for use of the Services.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on Aug 2009 

**Contacting Us**  

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

admin@anzac.co.in
